

Contact

- **** 9582955162,9267909075
- masterrajat102@gmail.com
- G-19 ,1st floor Mahindra Park ,Delhi -110033

Achievement

Qualified NET (subject:music) in session june 2024
Registeted Akhil Bhartiya Gandharva Mahavidyalaya teacher
Judged multiple musical Event of national level like Antaragini 2024
(IIT Kanpur) and events in Delhi
University
Conducts Grand Choirs at school and

Skill

Live Performer

university levels

- Music Teaching
- Mentorship
- Team Management
- Leadership
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking

Languages

- English (Fluent)
- Hindi (Fluent)
- Sindhi (Fluent)

RAJAT DHINGRA

Hindustani Classical /Semi Classical Vocalist -Teacher

Profile

I am a dedicated Indian Classical/Semi-Classical vocal artist and teacher with a strong foundation in Hindustani Classical music. With experience in leading choirs to success, I actively perform, judge, and teach classical choirs at both school and university levels, reaching students globally.

Work Experience

O Self Employed - Indian Music Teacher Provide Indian Music Classes to students from Country and Abroad	2019 - Present
O DHUNGURU Music Indian Music Teacher	2021 - Present
JAMPD Music Indian Music Teacher	2022 - Present
O Ambience Public School Indian Music Teacher	2024 - Present
O Mayoor School of Music Indian Music Teacher	2022 - 2024
Swarang Academy of Performing Arts	2019 - 2021
O Raaga -Indian Music Society of PGDAV College President and Vocal Instructor	2019 - 2020
O Raaga -Indian Music Society of PGDAV College Core Member and Vocalist	2017-2019
Education	

2021-2023

2015-2021

2017-2020

O Masters of Music (Hindustani Vocal Music)

Akhil Bhartiya Gandharva Mahavidyalaya Mandal

Visharad - Hindustani Classical Vocal

B.Sc (Hons.) Statistics

PGDAV College - Delhi University

Indira kala Sangit Vishwavidyalaya, Khairagarh University